<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<color name="markRed">#E31F04</color>
    <string name="app_name">Find Mark</string>
    <string name="TitlePictureContentDescription">True Love</string>
    <string name="MainMenuTestText">The <b>Love</b> Menu</string>
    <string name="BeginButtonText">Begin</string>
    <string name="ExitButtonText">Exit</string>
    <string name="AboutButtonText">About</string>
    <string name="SettingsButtonText">Settings</string>
	<string name="SettingsMenuText">Settings Menu</string>
    <string name="SoundOnOffCheckBoxText">Sounds On/Off</string>
    <string name="TitleImageText"><i>Touch The <b>Heart</b> Above To Continue</i></string>
    <string name="HappyValentines">Happy Valentine\'s "\n" Adriana</string>
    <string name="AboutTextTitle"><u>So, What Is This App About?</u></string>
    <string name="CorrectAnswerDialogBoxCheckBoxText">Show Correct Answer Pop-up Box</string>
    <string name="DebugModeCheckBoxText">Mark\'s Mode</string>
    
    <string name="AboutText">
Hi Adriana!
"\n"
"\n"
So, I created this Android Application..all for you! I thought that it would be cool to
create something unique for you. About 3 weeks ago, in late January, I was thinking what
to do for Valentines that you would remember and love me for. I had already booked a restaurant for Valentines Day, a
week before. And I was going to tell you about it, but thought I\'d leave it as a surprise. Then my mind 
started churning ideas about how to execute the surprise of the restaurant (Not a big surprise, I know). 
Anyhow, it occurred to me, to make you "find" me, or rather, to "find" out what restaurant I had booked!
I thought about making an activity, or giving you clues on Valentine\'s day, as to where I was. I wanted to make
it fun. But then again if you didn\'t find me, I would eat alone! If you were to find me, and I hope you do/did, then after 
the challenges, I would be the reward! Meee! But the challenges part escaped me. How was I to make you "find" me, the restaurant!
I didn\'t know what to do!
"\n"
"\n"
Then my light bulb moment came.    
"\n"
"\n"
I would create an Android game/application that you would play on Valentines day. The game would ask you multiple questions, about me, about you,
about my family, general knowledge and everything in between! But once the game is completed, it would reveal to you when and where I would be on
Valentine\'s day. That was my initial general idea. A simple one. So it did start out as a very simple concept, but that quickly became VERY
COMPLEX. I have had multiple releases of this game, of which I can show you. You will see the incremental amount of effort
I put into this. But it was worth it. You\'re worth it. Always.
"\n"
"\n"
But you are probably wondering, Mark, when did you get time to develop this?
"\n"
"\n"
Simple answer: It was at work. But really I did it at home too. Although it was next to impossible to code at home. I will
show you how Android Apps are developed, but nonetheless, at home I was only able to write code in a text editor as I could never
test it, since you would/might see the application on the computer. It was blind coding really!
"\n"
"\n"
But I didn\'t code during work hours (it was impossible), so most days, not everyday, when people would head home, I would start to code on this application after hours. 
Remember, I have never coded in Android before, so for a week I was clue less to what was going on. But 
after awhile things started to make sense and I was able to progress. The main iterations I did were as follows. I would create some code, test
it briefly on my work computer, then at the end of the day, create a signed release application [so it would install], send it to me on my phone, and mess with it on the bus
home. 
You won\'t believe the amount of issues I encountered on the bus and the lists I made of enhancements/fixes on the silver line!
Again, I\'ll show you everything and you\'ll understand the development process.
"\n"
"\n"
But I would do it again, all for you. I am very happy I did this. In the future, I will create more apps, maybe even
my NeVeX A.I. Engine for the Dots And Boxes Game. And that generally excites me!
"\n"
"\n"
So I thank you for giving me a reason to persist with this application, as without you, without my massive hunger to always make you happy,
to always make you love me, this application would never of happened! I have tried before to create Android applications, but 
failed as it becomes incredibly complicated very fast and I lose my focus and drive and I ultimately give up. But since I had a vision with this 
application, and since that vision was you, I of course, was going to complete it, or anything, because it involved you! 
"\n"
"\n"
You mean THAT much to me. And just so we are clear, THAT means EVERYTHING to me!
"\n"
"\n"
Anyhow my dear, enjoy the app, that is completely unqiue and made only for you! (But I do hope no bugs appear and it doesn\'t crash on you too!)
"\n"
"\n"
Happy Valentines!
"\n"
You Have All My Love,
"\n"
Mark.
"\n"
x
"\n"
"\n"
<b>P.S:</b>
"\n"
I hope you enjoy the music selection I picked!!
"\n"
"\n"
<b>P.P.S:</b>
"\n"
Fun Fact: This application version was finished at 3AM, 14th February, 2012, in our bed, with you asleep beside me! Thank God
you never woke to see this on my computer! 
"\n"
"\n"
    </string>
    
    <string name="GameIntroText"> 
        <u>Adriana! Please, Save Me!</u>
	</string>
    <string name="StartGameButton">Rescue Your True Love!</string>
    <string name="GameIntroBodyText">
Baby! I [Mark] have being kidnaped by my arch nemesis <b>KraM</b>!
He is holding me captive in this very nice restaurant!
"\n"
"\n"
Will you come save me? 
"\n"
"\n"
If so, then I have left a trail to my location. But in the form of cryptic clues! 
Only the one who <u>knows my heart</u>, shall find me and save me from this food....I mean <b>KraM</b>!
Note: You must <u>answer the clues from the <b>first person perspective</b></u>!
"\n"
"\n"
Begin your <b>love</b> quest and use your <b>infinite wisdom</b> to save me from <b>impending doom</b>!
"\n"
I trust you will succeed (like seriously, <u>you better succeed</u>) and I await your rescue!
"\n"
   	</string> 
    
    <string name="GameEndText">
        <u>Huzzah! You Love Mark!</u>
    </string>
        <string name="EndGameBodyTextBefore">
Baby! You\'ve completed the quest of<i>love</i>!
"\n"
Now that the journey has ended, I bestow onto you the ancient text, that will help you locate my whereabouts:
   	</string> 
	<string name="ResturantText">
	    <b>Da Vinci Restaurant</b>"\n"
	    <b>162 Columbus Ave</b>"\n"
	    <b>Boston, MA</b>"\n"
	    <b>02116</b>
    </string>
	<string name="EndGameBodyTextAfterFirst">
But wait! 
"\n"
"\n"
I have overheard <b>KraM\'s</b> minions state that he plans to have a committed relationship with
me (or something awfully horrible along those lines!) at about 8pm tonight!
"\n"
"\n"
Will you save me before <b>KraM</b> has had his way with me?
"\n"
"\n"
Also, I have read the ancient scriptures before and I came across this passage that I could not translate.
This passage of text, once spoken, is said to destroy <b>KraM</b> and save the cheerleader, which in turn will save
the world. But I cannot convert the passage text into <b>English</b>. It is too complicated for me.
"\n"
"\n"
However, can you attempt it? If you can translate and then <b><u>communicate the translation</u></b>, 
I may be be able to set myself free from <b>KraM\'s</b> clutches!
"\n"
"\n"
Quick! The Ancient text reads:
	</string>
	
	<string name="AncientText">
	    Los dioses han hablado: Sólo la mujer morena sexy tendrá el corazón del hombre blanco, para siempre.
    </string>
    
	<string name="EndGameBodyTextAfterSecond">
So, can you understand this ancient, wonderful text, that the gods have foreseen and written as fate? One would say that the
above text is "destiny inscribed". <u>What ever could that mean?!</u>
"\n"
"\n"
Alas! If you can translate <i>(even roughly! :-P )</i> then <u><b>communicate</b></u> it to me via carrier pigeons and the like!
"\n"
"\n"
Always know that I love you, as I anxiously await your <b><i>pigeon</i></b>!
"\n"
"\n"
   </string>
	
	<string name="GameEndButton">Save Mark!</string>
	
	
</resources>
